(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T13:09:55.424124",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
GUESTS + ANNOUNCEMENT!
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025
[Guests & Announcement! Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025]
ANYA MELFISSA
[Guest: Anya Melfissa]
KOBO KANAERU
[Guest: Kobo Kanaeru]
MOONA HOSHINOVA
[Guest: Moona Hoshinova]
KUREIJI OLLIE
[Guest: Kureiji Ollie]
TSUNOMAKI WATAME
[Guest: Tsunomaki Watame]
TAKANASHI KIARA
[Guest: Takanashi Kiara]
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
[Guest: Nerissa Ravencroft]
IIDA POCHI.
[Guest: Pochi Iida]
弄られて ただ流す
Toyed with, letting it flow away,
音のない音は招く
the soundless sound invites us in.
名前を捨てたのね
You threw away your name, didn't you?
あなたのモザイクが泣いてる
Your mosaic is weeping.
can not, can not, not, not, not deny
紛れもなく真実
undeniably the truth.
さあ預けて 回帰するように
Now entrust it, as if returning home,
エネルギーはサイクル そういまは
energy is a cycle, yes, right now.
無重力 象徴的なパレード
Zero gravity, a symbolic parade.
この月夜に 仰げ仰げ
Look up, look up into this moonlit night.
completeness
嗚呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, holding high the light of life.
KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu da 欺いて
KiLL KiSS, deceiving you,
KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu da 抱きしめて
KiLL KiSS, hold me tight.
ねえ 無防備だね
Hey, you're so defenseless.
美しい戯れに 人は壊れてゆく おかしいわね
People break down in a beautiful play. It's funny, isn't it?
cuz we're all alone
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even when you bite down,
手を挙げ 希え
raise your hand and wish for it.
oh, when you bleed, 惑星にそう その影を伸ばせ
Oh, when you bleed, stretch that shadow onto the planet.
ねえ 私の世界が 知りたがっているわそう
Hey, my world wants to know, yes.
you bleed, yes bleed, その血で 天の五線譜を書き換えれば
You bleed, yes bleed, if you rewrite heaven's staff with that blood—
code 'KiLL KiSS' uh...
KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu da 欺いて
KiLL KiSS, deceiving you,
KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu de KiLL KiSS chuu da 抱きしめて
KiLL KiSS, hold me tight.
ねえ 赤からさまね
Hey, it's so blatant.
醜い終局に すべてが変わってゆく
Everything changes into an ugly finale,
儚いのね
so ephemeral, isn't it?
そう このまま 壊れて
Yes, breaking just like this...
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY 細胞レベルに不毛に昂じょってる
BREAK AWAY, BREAK AWAY, barrenly stirred at the cellular level,
姿仕草超綺麗でしょ
your posture and gestures are super pretty, right?
don't you think? don't you think?
I'm so lazy 多分そう fine sound 並べただけの人 trash trash
I'm so lazy, probably so, fine sound, people just lining things up, trash, trash!
toss away don't you think? don't you think?
in this world この頭には what a beautiful 舞い得る花びらバラライカ 飲みたいな
In this world, in this head, what beautiful dancing petals, balalaika, I want to drink!
誰もが泣いた CR詠ZY 一瞬の感情に
Everyone cried, CR詠ZY, into a fleeting emotion.
RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON 心は95
RIDE ON, RIDE ON, RIDE ON, RIDE ON, my heart is 95!
狂気のサムライ 血走らせた目で 引くくらい狂い死だい
Samurai of madness, with bloodshot eyes, going crazy enough to make you pull back.
陽は昇り あなたの空 真っ黒な空
The sun rises, your sky, a pitch-black sky.
荒々しく引き千切って その場所で聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Wildly tearing it apart, the mechanism of the heartbeat heard right there.
驚くのは己の調べ 誰かのじゃない己の調べ
What's surprising is your own melody, not someone else's, your own melody.
目の前に広がる 世界はblue
Before my eyes, the world is blue.
ひとまず さぁ move move
For now, come on, move, move.
speak about 生き方
Speak about how to live,
there's no need
何をそんなに張り切って偉そうに
Why are you trying so hard and acting so high and mighty?
give me more 愛を
Give me more love.
右も左も 知りもしないで笑いだ
Laughing without knowing either right or left.
don't you think? don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
A grinning shadow laughs.
世界は大概
The world is mostly
c-r-a-z-y
繰り返すように ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
As if repeating, ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on.
わかってもいない
Not even understanding,
アレコレ authorize
authorizing this and that.
tell me something for the
偉大な期待の時代のバイブル
bible of an era of great expectations.
clap back
losin' my mind shooting my side
save it あなたのその瞬間 maybe nothing wrong nothing wrong
Save it, that moment of yours, maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong.
誰もがだいたい
Everyone is mostly
c-r-a-z-y
一瞬の感情に ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
Riding on momentary emotions, ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on.
心は95
The heart is 95.
狂気のサムライ
A samurai of madness.
血走らせた目で引きずるように ready to die
With bloodshot eyes, dragging along, ready to die.
ハロー 陽は昇り
Hello, the sun rises,
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
your sky, a pitch-black sky.
荒々しく 引きちぎって
Wildly tearing it apart.
ホラ その場所で 聞こえてくる 鼓動の仕掛け
Look, right there, the mechanism of the heartbeat can be heard.
驚くのは まだこれから まだこれから
The surprise is yet to come, yet to come.
嗟呼 もう待ちわびて
Ah, already waiting eagerly,
時計の針 零時の街
the clock hands, the town at midnight.
猛々しく いざ raise your voice
Fiercely, now, raise your voice.
ホラ すぐそこで 始まり出す 孤国の宴
Look, right there, the banquet of solitude begins.
奏でるのは 己の調べ 唯一無二の 己の調べ
What is played is one's own melody, a one-and-only melody.
わあーい！
Yay!
Perhatian, sang putri merak yang tertiup angin... Aku Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID! Attention please! I'm Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2.
Attention, the wind-blown peacock princess... I'm Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID! Attention please! I'm Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2.
皆様ごきげんよう、私 Hololive Indonesia 2期生 パボリア・レイネと申しますの！And welcome to Pavolia Reine's P.F.O. of the Blue Flame! Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 birthday! Welcome!
Greetings, everyone. I am Pavolia Reine, 2nd generation of Hololive Indonesia. And welcome to Pavolia Reine's P.F.O. of the Blue Flame! Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 birthday! Welcome!
Yeah! ようこそ！ええと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして...
Yeah! Welcome! Um, there's a hashtag on the upper left...
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner. It reads #ReineMEPtember2025, which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past a few years, yeah?
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner. It reads #ReineMEPtember2025, which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything, you can write it and I'll be looking forward to them. ご感想 and everything you guys can write. campur-campur dengan ngomongnya, aduh ya, gitu deh pokoknya.
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything, you can write it and I'll be looking forward to them. Thoughts and everything you guys can write. Mixing up the languages when speaking, oh well, you know how it is.
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live! You don't have to write it now, i'majinasi gak apa-apaですけど、I will be waiting! Yeah, so just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live! You don't have to write it now, imagining is fine too, but I will be waiting! Yeah, so just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage. Look at this! It's so cool, right? There's a mysterious flame, mysterious locks, mysterious cans, mysterious... where's the liquid? There was like a blue liquid there, but I mean, you saw it, right? Yeah!
If you... um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know, usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? それこそあの、火といえばですね、赤のイメージが強いかもしれません が...
If you... um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know, usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? Naturally, when thinking of fire, you might strongly associate it with the color red, but...
um, but actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Ya nggak sih? But actually, 実はですね、青い炎が一番強いと、思います！Yeah.
um, but actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Right? But actually, I think the blue flame is the strongest! Yeah.
So that's the theme of today's birthday! I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through hot songs and songs that will make you feel aduh, rangu banget, so atsui, so woof, gitu! Pokoknya just look forward to it, okay?
So that's the theme of today's birthday! I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through hot songs and songs that will make you feel oh, so passionate, so hot, so woof! Anyway, just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs you've sent today... uh, we have two songs. The first one was Kill Kiss. それってすごい好きな曲で、阿部真央様の Kill Kiss です。And then the second song was... uh, what I was really, really like from Proseca, the unit Vivid BAD SQUAD's, uh, 'Crazy' deshita!
And the songs you've sent today... uh, we have two songs. The first one was Kill Kiss. It's a song I really like, Abe Mao-sama's 'Kill Kiss'. And then the second song was... uh, what I really, really like from Proseca, the unit Vivid BAD SQUAD's, uh, 'Crazy'!
And the second song was 'Crazy' from... a unit I really, really like from Proseca, Vivid BAD SQUAD. I hope you guys enjoyed it! Yay! Emang kayak ya, Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya.
And the second song was 'Crazy' from... a unit I really, really like from Proseca, Vivid BAD SQUAD. I hope you guys enjoyed it! Yay! It's like, Reine really, really loves the songs...
Jadi masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs, and I'm sure there's a lot of guests. I hope you guys are excited for them! So, dari sekarang nih, makin makin panas karena nanti guests-nya many, many, many, many, many! So, please look forward to it!
So there are still going to be a lot more. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs, and I'm sure there's a lot of guests. I hope you guys are excited for them! So, starting from now, it's gonna get even hotter because the guests will be many, many, many, many, many! So, please look forward to it!
But for now, I'm going to sing
one of my original songs, do you guys know what it is?
The next song is Love Me Love Me.
ずっと 君のとなり じっと見てる 分かり合い
Always right beside you, watching intently, understanding each other.
止まない雨 世界に二人きり
An endless rain, just the two of us in this world.
刻むようにしと 今この手にと
Etching it into our hands right now,
痛みさえも愛の形
Even the pain is a form of love.
運命に結ばれた 小指握る 約束をしよう
Let's make a promise, holding pinkies bound by fate.
Love Me Love Me
私がいらない
I don't need you,
君がいらない
I don't need anyone else.
Love Me Love Me
君がいらない
I don't need you,
I don't need you.
ぎゅっと 抱きしめたら きっと 逃げられない
If you hold me tight, surely I won't be able to escape.
チクタック 針が回る 世界に二人きり
Tick-tock, the hands of the clock turn, just the two of us in this world.
秩序壊すように 感情推し殺して
As if breaking order, killing our emotions,
秘密さえも愛のメロディ
Even our secrets are a love melody.
運命に結ばれた 小指握る 約束をしよう
Let's make a promise, holding pinkies bound by fate.
私がいらない
I don't need you,
I don't need you.
Love Me Love Me
君がいらない
I don't need you,
I don't need you.
愛して 愛されて 離れられない
Loving and being loved, we can never part.
You & Me 二人きりでいい
You & Me, just the two of us is fine.
Give Me Your Love
願い合うほど 私達は若い
The more we wish for each other, the closer we get.
何もかも全て知るくらいを
Wanting to know everything about each other,
もっと頂戴
Give me more!
私がいらない
I don't need you,
I don't need you.
Love Me Love Me
君がいらない
I don't need you,
I don't need you.
Love Me Love Me
da na na na na na na na na
wake up, get up, stand up, mera
まあこんなもんでいいかは そろそろやめにしようや
Let's quit settling for "good enough."
手抜き手に入れた無理 それを大事にするのがお前の売り？
Is your selling point holding on to cut corners?
いつかくる後悔を消せるかは今の自分次第
Whether you can erase future regrets depends on who you are now.
やるだけやったれ 誰じゃなくて 自分の自分に嫌われないように
Just do your best, so you won't hate yourself later.
比べちまうの毒 目の前夢の壁だけ knock knock
Comparing yourself is poison; just knock on the wall of your dreams.
大層な理想それで結構 ああとはひたすら前に進むだけ
Grand ideals are fine; just keep moving straight ahead.
バカにされればされるほど 叶えた時が爽快だろ
The more you're mocked, the more exhilarating it is when you achieve it.
まだいけるはず まだやれるはず
You can still go on, you can still do this!
やば badな burnout ぶっかます番だ
It's time to smash through that bad burnout!
さあ歌え 踊れ 騒え つかびびってんのか ha ha
Now sing, dance, get wild—what, are you scared? Haha!
やば badな burnout かっ飛ばす場外
A bad burnout, hitting it right out of the park!
頭で決めた限界なんて 当然一点超突破
Limits decided in your head are meant to be smashed.
だだだだだら いいねその感じ
Da-da-da-da-da, yeah, that's the feeling!
だだだだだら いいエゴの暗示
Da-da-da-da-da, a great egoistic suggestion!
“最高”の見学に行くヤツ集合 音の鳴るほうへ
Gather around, those going to see the "ultimate"—head toward the sound!
やば badな burnout ぶっかます番だ
It's time to smash through that bad burnout!
さあ歌え 踊れ 騒え 上がれ まだまだ足んねえなあ
Now sing, dance, get wild, rise up—it's still not enough!
まだまだmera mera
Still burning more and more!
ガンガン登る 今は何合目？ 二進や三進ぽで頂上に
Climbing hard, what station are we at? Advancing inch by inch to the peak.
何があったって 俺は俺 どんどん進め 見てろ後悔め
No matter what happened, I am me, keep pushing forward and watch regrets fade.
馬鹿にされてからが本番 下馬評のひっくり返しはロマン
The real show starts after being mocked; overturning underdog reviews is romantic.
重ねる努力から打ち下ろす k.o.
Landing a knockout blow built from accumulated effort!
さあ今日も勇敢な俺は
Now, brave as ever today,
ドラマみたいに輝く毎日じゃないけど
My days aren't shining like a drama,
友がいて あの子がいて できるだけの恋があって
With friends, that special someone, and all the love I can give,
頑張っていこうぜ オーイェー未来が輝くように
Let's do our best, oh yeah, so the future shines bright.
精一杯の不器用ダンス オーイェー誰それ気にすんな
With all my clumsy dance, oh yeah, don't worry about who's who,
オリジナルのジタバタダンス
My very own flailing dance!
さあ今日も勇敢な俺は 敬遠を強引にスイング
Now, brave as ever today, taking a bold swing at caution,
作戦は当たって砕けろ 恋心爆発させた
Strategy is hit-or-miss, letting my romantic feelings explode.
ドラフト外と言われりゃ オイラだって凹むさ
If they call me a non-draft pick, even I get down.
月を見て 涙して あくびして ごまかして
Looking at the moon, crying, yawning to brush it off,
頑張っていこうぜ
Let's do our best!
オーイェー未来が輝くように
Oh yeah, so the future shines bright.
精一杯の不器用ダンス
With all my clumsy dance,
オーイェー誰それ気にすんな
Oh yeah, don't worry about who's who,
オリジナルのジタバタダンス
My very own flailing dance!
オーイェー未来をあの日のために
Oh yeah, for the future of that day,
青春の汗を流してダンス
Dancing with the sweat of youth.
オーイェー誰だって出来るはず
Oh yeah, anyone should be able to do it,
オリジナルのジタバタダンス
My very own flailing dance!
どん底を見て笑える
Being able to smile looking from the rock bottom,
そんな力こそ 今しかない
Such strength is only available now,
やるしかない 溢れ出すジタバタダンス
We've got to do it, overflowing flailing dance!
頑張っていこうぜ オーイェー未来が輝くように
Let's do our best, oh yeah, so the future shines bright.
精一杯の不器用ダンス
With all my clumsy dance,
オーイェー誰それ気にすんな
Oh yeah, don't worry about who's who,
オリジナルのジタバタダンス
My very own flailing dance!
オーイェー未来をあの日のために
Oh yeah, for the future of that day,
青春の汗を流してダンス
Dancing with the sweat of youth.
オーイェー誰だって出来るはず
Oh yeah, anyone should be able to do it,
オリジナルのジタバタダンス
My very own flailing dance!
どん底を見て笑える まだまだ踊れよ
Smiling from rock bottom, keep on dancing!
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誘惑される鼓動に
To the heartbeat that tempts me,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers to love in the bursting struggles,
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
Love is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
Piercing right through someone,
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, step to your own beat.
仕事帰りの疲れは 私と、このグラスに
After a hard day's work, share it with me and this glass.
さあ 自分好みに染まって 世間に対する気持ち
Now, embrace your own style and pour out your feelings to me,
私に注いでみない?
How about it?
ありそうなラブソングでも 愛が込められてるの
It may be a common love song, but it's filled with love.
それでも汚れるのね 君を見れば分かるの
Even so, it gets tainted; I can tell just by looking at you.
下を向く君の目を 無理矢理剥がそうとはしないから
I won't force you to look up when your eyes are cast down,
そんな顔せず手を差し伸べてほら
So don't make that face, just reach out your hand, come on.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誘惑される鼓動に
To the heartbeat that tempts me,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers to love in the bursting struggles,
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
Love is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
Piercing right through someone,
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
君の愛を知った気で
Thinking I knew your love,
ハイになっていて
I was flying high,
感度欠いていて
Losing all sense,
毎度泣いていてさ
Crying every single time.
それくらいがいいんでしょう
That's what you want, isn't it?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, step to your own beat.
君の顔色 今では
Your complexion's getting better
マシになってきているから
Now than before,
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll leave it to you, Bunny Girl.
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
You can have me, Bunny Girl.
誘惑される鼓動に
To the heartbeat that tempts me,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers to love in the bursting struggles,
伝えられるはず
I'm sure I can convey it.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
Piercing right through someone,
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, step to your own beat.
君の顔色 今では
Your complexion's getting better
マシになってきているから
Now than before,
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
You can have me, Bunny Girl.
誘惑される鼓動に
To the heartbeat that tempts me,
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers to love in the bursting struggles,
伝えられるはず
I'm sure I can convey it.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
The night is just beginning, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
Piercing right through someone,
澄んだ君の目を 孕んで
Embracing your clear eyes.
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
アー 星辰ならで ハイカイアイマイシャットダウン
Ah, floating through constellations, a high-key ambiguous shutdown.
結晶のラウェイ びえぎりワンダー
A crystal runway, a beautiful wonder.
彗星のステーション ならば今夜はmovin' to 選択肢
A comet's station—tonight we're movin' to our choices.
引っ込めダウンサイン バパサモージュトゥマイハート
Put away the down sign, bam bam, all the more choose to my heart!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
衝動現実からのescape ぬらりくらりSOS
Escaping from impulse and reality, slip-sliding away with an SOS.
なら燃え上がるわ全身
Then the whole body bursts into flames!
one chance 狙うjack pot 願いましょうgabut
Aiming for one chance, jack pot, let's make a wish, gabut.
のるかそるかkill or be killed look back show!
Sink or swim, kill or be killed, look back show!
感性 完成 完成 おそうじをけ・あ・ず・き・ず・き
Sensitivity, completion, completion—cleaning up carefully, azuki, azuki...
パラパッ サメないうちに
Para-pa, before it wears off!
あ・ず・き・ず・き パラパッ お・あ・じ・わ・い・か・が？
Azuki azuki, para-pa, how does it taste?
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
ああ 足りない まだ足りないな
Ah, it's not enough, still not enough!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
ああ ロンリーナイト まだ足りないな
Ah, a lonely night, still not enough!
右に左に抜けて 最高限界点更新中
Slipping right and left, breaking our peak limits.
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
思考のマリアージュ 駆け足ドメスティック
A marriage of thoughts, a fast-paced domestic rush.
右か左か逃げるが勝ちだ
Running away to the right or left is the winning move.
暴走中道中dug dug ガラ空きのdance hall
Rampaging midway, dug dug, an empty dance hall.
卵が先だピースは揃った！ sir
Which came first? The pieces are all set, sir!
baby baby baby もう時間がないわ
Baby, baby, baby, we're out of time!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
ラリルララ・ルリ すぐ前へてるらら
La-ri-lu-ra-ra-ru-ri, right ahead, te-ru-ra-ra.
壊れる前に ああ ドッキドッキパヤッパ ルージュを付けて
Before it breaks, ah, put on some thrilling pyapa rouge!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
あ・ず・き・ず・き パラパッ し・ふ・く・リ・ズ・ム
Azuki azuki, para-pa, supreme rhythm!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
ああ 足りない まだ足りないな
Ah, it's not enough, still not enough!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
ああ 範囲外 もう消えそうだ
Ah, out of range, about to vanish!
こっち向いてよ darling
Look this way, darling!
ヤミヤミヤミ
Yami yami yami...
痛いことは嫌いですが
I dislike painful things, but...
君の手の平は嫌いじゃない
I don't dislike the palm of your hand.
言葉は飴玉みたいに 甘く広がってココロ満たす
Words spread sweetness like hard candy, filling my heart.
髣髴 全然分かってない
Reminiscent? You totally don't get it.
永遠に言う通り 完全否定できない
Doing as you say forever, I can't fully deny it.
どこにいても
Wherever I am...
(なんてね分かってない)
(You don't get it at all.)
元々あの娘みたいに可愛くなれなくちゃ
I need to become as cute as that girl from the start!
愛嬌は序盤にしとこう はめ間に
Charm should be saved for the early game, caught in between.
盲点出たいのだって 分からなくなる
Wanting to escape my blind spot, I lose track of it.
永遠再び 主にご褒美 もうやんなくたってそれないように
Eternity once more, a reward from the master—so I won't lose my way anymore!
今日だってちゃんとナイショの毛繕い にゃんたを横にするから愛して
Today too, I'll secretly groom my fur and snuggle up, so please love me!
everybody today is rubbing day get it get it this is my courtship
any any any time is fine with me gimme gimme love me, my darling
会いたいお間違いなんて皆は言う 取リ憑かれているってならこの胸で疼く
Everyone says "wanting to see you" is a mistake, that I'm possessed, but it throbs right here in my chest.
締め付けるような切なさは何なの？ 選ぶ言葉と戸惑う指先 端正な横顔
What is this gripping pain? The words I choose, my hesitant fingertips, your neat profile...
(私しか知らない)
(Only I know.)
髣髴 ランダムご機嫌 もしかして今日は
Reminiscent, random moods—could it be that today...
優しく撫でてくれるのかな？
You'll gently stroke me?
君のソレが耐えられるの 生涯で私だけなんだよね
I'm the only one in this lifetime who can endure your quirks, right?
あからさまに カラダまさに 「もう嫌だ」って離れられないよね
So obviously, literally in body, you can't just walk away saying "I've had enough," right?
そうだよね？ 感情は上々に 訴えは少々に もうlieも詐欺のように
Right? Feelings are high-strung, complaints are minimal, lies are like scams now—
転がせば良い 柑橘の匂いだって凌ぐのだ
just roll with it, it even surpasses the scent of citrus.
もう噛んだって吠えられるだけだし 今日だってちゃんと
Biting just gets me scolded, so today too...
痛いことは嫌いですが
I hate it when it hurts, but
君の手の平は嫌いじゃない
I don't hate the palm of your hand.
言葉は飴玉みたいに
Words spread like candy drops
甘く広がってココロ満たす
And sweetly fill my heart.
吁呼 全然分かってない
Ah, you don't get it at all.
永遠に言う通り
Just follow instructions forever.
今日だってちゃんと
Even today, properly...
『はい 喜んで』
"Yes, I'd love to!"
『あなた方のため』
"For your sake."
『はい 謹んで』
"Yes, respectfully!"
『あなた方のため』
"For your sake."
差し伸べてきた手
The hand reached out to me,
さながら正義仕立て
framed as justice itself.
嫌々で生き延びて
Surviving reluctantly,
わからずやに盾
a shield against the stubborn.
『はい 喜んであなた方のために』
"Yes, gladly, for your sake!"
出来ることなら出来るどこまで
If I can, as far as I can!
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember all the things you hate,
奈落音頭奏でろ ドン・ドン・ドン
and play the abyss Ondo! Boom, boom, boom!
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take yet another step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember all the things you hate,
鳴らせ君の3から6マス トン・トン・トン・ツ・トン・トン
ring your 3 to 6 squares! Ton-ton-ton-tsu-ton-ton!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと鳴らせ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, ring it more!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと鳴らせ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, ring it more!
鳴らせ君の病いの町を ドン・ドン
Ring through your town of sickness, boom, boom!
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドン・ドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, boom, boom!
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを ドン・ドン
Throw away the superhumans of justice, boom, boom!
鳴らせ君の3から6マス トン・トン・トン・ツ・トン・トン
Ring your 3 to 6 squares! Ton-ton-ton-tsu-ton-ton!
怒り抱いても優しさが勝つ
Even when holding anger, kindness wins out.
あなたの欠けたとこが希望 Save this game mr. A
The parts where you are lacking are your hope—Save this game, mr. A.
救われたのは僕のうちの1人で
The one saved was just one of us...
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember all the things you hate,
奈落音頭奏でろ ドン・ドン・ドン
and play the abyss Ondo! Boom, boom, boom!
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take yet another step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember all the things you hate,
鳴らせ君の3から6マス
ring your 3 to 6 squares!
分かれ道思うがまま Go To Earth
On the branching path, go to earth as you please,
任せきりワガママな言葉 奏でろハクナマタタの音は トン・トン・トン・ツ・トン・トン
leaving it to selfish words—play the sound of Hakuna Matata! Ton-ton-ton-tsu-ton-ton!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと鳴らせ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, ring it more!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス 踊れ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, dance!
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス もっと鳴らせ
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance, ring it more!
鳴らせ君の病いの町を ドン・ドン
Ring through your town of sickness, boom, boom!
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドン・ドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, boom, boom!
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを ドン・ドン
Throw away the superhumans of justice, boom, boom!
鳴らせ君の3から6マス トン・トン・トン・ツ・トン・トン
Ring your 3 to 6 squares! Ton-ton-ton-tsu-ton-ton!
『はい 喜んであなた方のために』
"Yes, gladly, for your sake!"
出来ることなら出来るどこまで
If I can, as far as I can!
『はい 謹んであなた方のために』
"Yes, respectfully, for your sake!"
鳴らせ君の3から6マス トン・トン・トン・ツ・トン・トン
Ring your 3 to 6 squares! Ton-ton-ton-tsu-ton-ton!
あらぽちママ！
Ara pochimama!
読者の皆様こんにちは、お疲れ様です、一途ぽちです！
Hello readers, good work, it's Ichizu Pochi!
ママが教えてくれた言葉で、お嬢様も言葉で自己紹介します。
With the words mama taught me, I will introduce myself as an ojou-sama.
え、皆様ごきげんよう、わたくしパボリア・レイネ……あ、
Um, greetings everyone, I am Pavolia Reine... ah,
う、あ、ごきげんよう、リセットリセット、ごきげんようわたくし
u, ah, greetings, reset reset, greetings, I am
ホロライブインドネシア2期生パボリア・レイネと申しますの。以後お見知りおきを！
Hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen Pavolia Reine. Please remember me!
初お嬢様でございます！
It's my first time as an ojou-sama!
お嬢様ですわ、完全に。お嬢様配信！お嬢様ムービング！
I'm totally an ojou-sama. Ojou-sama stream! Ojou-sama moving!
お嬢様、あ、お嬢様ムービング。お嬢様ムービング。
Ojou-sama, ah, ojou-sama moving. Ojou-sama moving.
イェーイ！お嬢様ムービング！
Yay! Ojou-sama moving!
レイネちゃん、う、わ、お嬢様トークン！ハッピーバースデー！おめでとう！
Reine-chan, u, wa, ojou-sama token! Happy birthday! Congratulations!
え、さっきはバリーガールを一緒に歌いました！
Um, earlier we sang "Bari Girl" together!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
イェーイ！
Yay!
どうだった？踊れてた？
How was it? Could you dance?
もう腰が…
My lower back...
ノースジ、マッサージ、マッサージ。肩、肩お願いします、肩。あ、ありがとうございます！
Massage, massage. Shoulder, shoulder please, shoulders. Ah, thank you very much!
私もマッサージが欲しい！
I want a massage too!
はい、お、お疲れ様、ここですか？こちらですか？
Yes, oh, good work, is it here? Is it this way?
パーフェクトでございます！
It is perfect!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Pochi-mama and Reine! Nobody girl!
Yeah!
お父様ハイテンションで 今日も素晴らしいです さすがわです
Father is in high spirits today as well. Truly wonderful!
はりね today
Hari-ne today...
Pochi-mama, did you guys see last time Pochi-mama's 3D ohirome?
Pochi-mama, did you guys see last time Pochi-mama's 3D reveal?
そう、2人で私の2人のひろめで、れいねちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました。皆さん見ていただけましたでしょうか？
Yes, at my 3D reveal, I sang and danced together with Reine-chan. Did everyone watch it?
And because of that, today I invited Pochi-mama to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
Yeah, yeah. No, thank you, thank you. Thank you for coming, I had so much fun.
めっちゃ楽しいねねねねねね
So much fun, ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
What should we talk about? If I remember Pochi-mama, I remember...
お嬢様。
Ojou-sama.
Because back then, I thought...
I'm a princess. So I have to act like a princess.
お嬢様だから、あの日本語で、お嬢様、お嬢様エティングひつよひつよげで、guys.
Because you're an ojou-sama, ojou-sama acting is necessary, guys.
もう、これで完璧です、さっきの動きで。
This is already perfect, with those movements from earlier.
あ、ジャンプで、あ、こっちの、こっちの動きですか？こっちで、こっちで、お嬢様の。
Ah, with a jump, this movement? Over here, the ojou-sama one!
皆さんもお嬢様、お嬢様になりたい方はね、ちょっとしてください。ちょっとって、何ですか？ちょっと、ちょっと、まねしてください。
Everyone who wants to become an ojou-sama, please do this a bit. Please imitate a bit.
そう、こんな動きが、お嬢様ですよ。本当にいいんですかね、これで。
Yes, this movement is very ojou-sama! Is this really okay?
ちなみに、あのネタバレになると思うんですが、あの、今日のグッズはね、誕生日グッズはね、Pochi-mamaが頑張りました!
By the way, I think this is a spoiler, but today's birthday merch—Pochi-mama worked hard on it!
書かせていただきました、皆さん!ちゃんとグッズ紹介まで最後までしっかり見てくださいね、よろしくお願いします。
I drew it, everyone! Please watch the merch introduction until the end, thank you.
Yeah! Pokonya, katanya, jangan ke mana-mana, guys. Pokonya, tunggu sampai akhir.
Yeah! Anyway, don't go anywhere, guys. Anyway, wait until the end.
Karena ada goods dari Pochi-mama-sensei. Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan, kan? Makanya, tonton sampai habis, oke?
Because there are goods from Pochi-mama-sensei. You don't want to miss it, right? Watch until the end, okay?
Thank you, Pochi-mama, for coming! Thank you! Thank you!
この後もライブが続くので、楽しんでね！ Yeah! Yay!
The live continues after this, so please enjoy! Yeah! Yay!
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai Scream!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you.
Tell me more, tell me more, tell me more
聞かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice.
Let me hear more, let me hear more, let me hear more
こんなドキドキもう最近れないよ
Such pounding excitement—I can't take it anymore lately!
Oh, I need you, oh, I need you
戸惑いは捨て 今日生の私に続けてほしいの
Cast aside hesitation and keep following today's brand-new me!
勇気を出して 見つめる作戦
Gather your courage, the strategy to gaze...
瞳が合えば 止められないよ
When our eyes meet, I can't stop it!
この恋 この愛で メロメロ溶けちゃうよ
This romance, this love will melt you completely!
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいてマイカリー 届けて 大好き
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling—deliver my greatest love!
I like la la la love me more
リビちゃん！
Ribichan!
はい！何が好き？
Yes! What do you like?
チョコレート！よりもあなた！あゆむちゃん！
Chocolate! More than that, you! Ayumichan!
はい！何が好き？
Yes! What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバー！よりもあなた！しきちゃん！
Strawberry flavor! More than that, you! Shikichan!
はい！何が好き？
Yes! What do you like?
クッキーアンドクリーム！よりもあなた！みんな！
Cookies and cream! More than that, you! Everyone!
はい！何が好き？
Yes! What do you like?
もちろん大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course, we love ice cream!
止められない
We can't stop!
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this love
メル・メルティ・とろけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm melting
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice, "my darling"
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out, because I love you!
Love, scream, 叫ぼう
Love, scream, let's scream
Scream, アイスクリーム
Scream, ice cream
Okay!
Love, scream, 叫ぼう
Love, scream, let's scream
Scream, アイスクリーム
Scream, ice cream
Ruby-chan?
Yes~?
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント、でも君の方が好き！
Chocolate mint, but I like you more!
Ayumu-chan?
Yes?
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリー、でも君の方が好き！
Strawberry flavour, but I like you more!
Shiki-chan?
Yes?
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリーム、でも君の方が好き！
Cookies and cream, but I like you more!
Everyone?
Yes?
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん、愛してる、AiScReam!
Of course, I love you, AiScReam!
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this love
メル・メルティ・とろけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm melting
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice, "my darling"
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out, because I love you!
(One) 勇気出して
(One) Summon up the courage
(Two) 見つめる作戦
(Two) Strategy of gazing
(Three) 目が合ったら
(Three) When our eyes meet
(Fall) 止まらない
(Fall) Unstoppable
この恋 この愛で
With this love, this love
メル・メルティ・とろけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm melting
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice, "my darling"
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out, because I love you!
Love, scream, 叫ぼう
Love, scream, let's scream
Scream, アイスクリーム
Scream, ice cream
Okay!
Love, scream, 叫ぼう
Love, scream, let's scream
Scream, アイスクリーム
Scream, ice cream
見つけて、 "my darling"
Please find, "my darling"
気づいて、 "my darling"
Please notice, "my darling"
(One) 勇気出して
(One) Summon up the courage
(Two) アプローチ作戦
(Two) Approach strategy
(Three) 手を触れて
(Three) Touching hands
(Fall) 止まらない
(Fall) Can't stop
Yeah, yeah, yeah, この愛で、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this love, this love
メル・メルティ・とろけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm melting
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice, "my darling"
君だよ、only one!
That's you, only one!
Love, scream, 叫ぼう
Love, scream, let's scream
Scream, アイスクリーム
Scream, ice cream
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
白鳥たちはそう
'Cause even swans, you know
見えないところでバタ足するんです
Flutter their legs where they can't be seen
本能に順従 忠実
I'm true to my instincts, though
翻弄も重々承知
I accept I'll be constantly ridiculed
前途洋々だし…
I got a bright future, after all...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Which is why I'll take a rest sometimes
Don't say "lazy"
その目でしっかり見定めて
With your own eyes, ascertain it carefully
行き先地図上マークして
And mark it on your map
近道あればそれが王道
When there's a shortcut, you got a right
はしょる翼あれば上等
Even better if you got some wings tucked away
ヤバ 爪割れた
Crap, you break a nail
グループで補修した
then fix it with glue
それだけでなんか達成感
And just that gives a sense of achievement
大事なのは自分 かわいがること
The most important thing is to care for yourself
自分を愛さないと 他人も愛せない
You gotta love yourself before you can love
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
能ある鷹はそう 見えないところにピック隠すんです
'Cause even the skilled hawk hides his picks
想像に一生懸命 現実は絶体絶命
Dream with all you got, 'cause reality's hard
発展途中だし… だから不意にピッチ外れちゃうんです
I'm still growing, after all...
その目に映らないだけで やる気はメーター振り切って
Even though it's not in front of you
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
新たな顔と見えないところにピーク隠すんです
'Cause even peacocks wait till the time is right
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Always try to dream and sleep with all your might
ヤリ ちょっと痩せた 調子づいて暴飲した
Awesome, you get thinner and eat happily
それだけでなんで？敗北感
And just that, why? Makes you feel defeated
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
You have to lower your expectations
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Those that adapt quickly win
その目に映らないだけだって
Even though it's not in front of you
やる気はメーター振り切って
Your will is a meter long
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always try to dream with all your might
いつでも全力を駆使して
その分全力で眠って
And to the same extent, sleep with all your might
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
'Cause even swans, you know, flutter their legs
本能に順従忠実 翻弄も重々承知
I'm true to my instincts, though I accept ridicule
前途洋々だし…
I got a bright future, after all...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Which is why I'll take a rest sometimes
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
だけど本当はcrazy
白鳥たちはそう 見えないところでバタ足するんです
Swans, you see, flutter their legs where they can't be seen.
本能に順従 忠実 翻弄も重々承知
True to my instincts, faithful, fully aware of the teasing.
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休息しちゃうんです
My future is bright... so I take a little rest sometimes.
この目でしっかと見定めて 行き先地図上マークして
Carefully gazing with my own eyes, marking destinations on the map.
Hey!
夢は全力で 現実はレディー
Dream with all your might, reality is a lady.
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休息しちゃうんです
My future is bright... so I take a little rest sometimes.
この目でしっかと見定めて 行き先地図上マークして
Carefully gazing with my own eyes, marking destinations on the map.
近道あればそれが王道 はしゃげる翼があれば上等
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road; if you have wings, even better.
ヤバ 爪折れた グルーで補修した
Crap, broke a nail, repaired it with glue.
それだけでなんだか達成感 自分可愛がること
Just that gives me a sense of achievement; caring for yourself,
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
You gotta love yourself before you can love others.
自分を許せないやつは人も許せない
Those who can't forgive themselves can't forgive others either.
Please don't say “You are lazy”
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
能ある鷹はそう 見えないところにピック隠すんです
The talented hawks, you know, hide their picks where they can't be seen.
夢は全力で 現実はレディー
Dream with all your might, reality is a lady.
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休息しちゃうんです
My future is bright... so I take a little rest sometimes.
この目でしっかと見定めて 行き先地図上マークして
Carefully gazing with my own eyes, marking destinations on the map.
近道あればそれが王道 はしゃげる翼があれば上等
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road; if you have wings, even better.
ヤバ 爪折れた グルーで補修した
Crap, broke a nail, repaired it with glue.
Waaah, bagaimana? Was it wasn't the gondola and the bazooka
Waaah, how was it? Wasn't the gondola and the bazooka
and the bazooka and everything very cool? We've listened to so many songs,
and everything very cool? We've listened to so many songs,
but there's still more!
Here's the long awaited...
Here's the long-awaited...
God's show-kai! 今回も生誕グッズがあります!
God showcase! This time we also have birthday merchandise!
まずはこちらですね 青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット
First is this one, the Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat.
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat ini seperti dijanjikan ya,
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat, just as promised, ya,
totally no spoiler, made by Pochimama!
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mat/desk mat,
and so we have another one! And for those of you who already have that rubber mat, well, here's adek-kakak beda, it's different! Yay!
and so we have another one! And for those who already have the previous one, well, here it's different, yay!
And along with the rubber mat, we have the tapestry!
Yay! Ini kalian tidak tergoreng ya, kalian tidak tergoreng.
Yay! You guys aren't getting fried, right? You aren't getting fried.
Sesuai tema live dari kali ini, we have... 青い炎の孔雀タペストリー!
According to the live's theme this time, we have... the Peafowl of the Blue Flame Tapestry!
Dan selanjutnya adalahこちらですね! Mana nih lanjutannya buat kalian yang suka minimalist design, we have Blooming Flame Coaster!
And next is this one! For those of you who like minimalist designs, we have the Blooming Flame Coaster!
Dan pokoknya temanya itu cocok banget sama tapestry-nya dan juga rubber mat-nya yang tadi ya, ilustrasi Pochimama. Jadi mendingan...
And basically the theme matches the tapestry and the rubber mat by Pochimama, so you better...
...masukkan ke keranjang sekarang juga! Eh, belum bisa ya? Ya udahlah enggak apa-apa.
...add it to your cart right now! Eh, can't yet? Ah, well, never mind.
And then, next one, sana nih, ada juga seperti biasa, ada voice! Karena Reine suka sekali sushi, because I love sushi so much, sushi-daisuki Reine ga membuat "Secret Sushi Strategy" Voice Pack!
And then next up, over here, we also have, as usual, a voice pack! Because Reine loves sushi so much, I made the "Secret Sushi Strategy" Voice Pack!
Untuk kalian yang suka sushi juga mungkin ya. Let's go!
For those of you who like sushi too, perhaps. Let's go!
Terakhir nih, full set-to o-kou-nyuu-itadai-ta-kata ni wa... buat yang beli full set akan ada...
Lastly, for those who purchase the full set... for those who buy the full set, there will be...
...suryou gentei de chokuhitsu message to haku-oshi fukusei sign iri postcard ga tsuite-kimasu!
...limited edition postcards with handwritten messages and foil-stamped replicated signatures included!
And then, next up, I'm gonna introduce my new song. See? Well, I don't know, this is my first...
Sometimes doing this genre, I'm a little bit shy.
It's a little bit different from what I usually sing, so I hope
you guys can... even, yeah, if if it could resonate with you guys even for a little, I would be so happy.
you guys can... well, if it can resonate with you guys even a little, I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするのは初めてでした。
This is my first time singing a genre like this.
だからね、ちょっと恥ずかしいです。
So, yeah... I'm a bit shy.
Yeah, well, basically, well, being placed in a box you don't exactly fit, it sucks, right?
Yeah, well, basically, being placed in a box you don't exactly fit, it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know, it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you you, and even if you're broken, it's fine, and no one else's opinions should change that.
And sometimes your flaws are what make you you, and even if you're broken, it's fine, and no one else's opinion should change that.
とにかく自分をありのままを愛していいよって曲です。
Anyway, it's a song about loving your true self just as you are.
じゃあ、あの、これから準備するので待っててね！
So, um, I'm going to go prepare now, so please wait!
Please wait 'cause I'm going to prepare, I got a surprise!
Yay! Bye-bye!
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyat who just can't wait for when I'm going to implement a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership. (That is me, by the way.)
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to briefly explain what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership (that is me, by the way).
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights, which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and a sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties, which also means membership-exclusive streams, in which we can have various talks, play games together, and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties, which also means membership-exclusive streams where we can chat, play games together, and do other member activities.
Like what, you might ask? Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is... SAFETY IS GUARANTEED. Welcome to the Royaltea.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Hey ! hey ! hey !
Hey! Hey! Hey!
( never never , never gonna figure it out ! )
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out!)
hey ! hey ! hey !
Hey! Hey! Hey!
( never gonna figure it out ! )
(Never gonna figure it out!)
wake up , another bloody monday
Wake up, another bloody Monday
say things i never wanted to say
up in arms
who can i please ?
Up in arms, who can I please?
you ?
livin ’ day by day
You? Livin' day by day
wake up , another bloody monday
Wake up, another bloody Monday
rinse & repeat until it ’s sunday
Rinse & repeat until it's Sunday
hold it , so frustrated
Hold it, so frustrated
ya know i can ’t do it no more ~
Ya know I can't do it no more~
i ’ll say ~
I'll say~
no good , down to the core
No good, down to the core
hear you knockin , beat in ’ down my door !
Hear you knockin', beatin' down my door!
yell out , scream and shout
Yell out, scream and shout
but i ’ll never change it now
But I'll never change it now
i ’m just too much but not enough to please you , right ?
I'm just too much but not enough to please you, right?
[ no i ’m never , never gonna - ]
[No I'm never, never gonna-]
your idea of ideals that you ’re screaming in my ear
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
i ’m just so broken ~
I'm just so broken~
never , never , never gonna figure it out !
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
hey ! hey !
Hey! Hey!
i ’ll stop me !
I'll stop me!
hey ! hey !
Hey! Hey!
i ’ll never figure it out ~ !
I'll never figure it out~!
hey ! hey !
Hey! Hey!
never never , never gonna figure it out
Never never, never gonna figure it out
you want me to know what i just don ’t know
You want me to know what I just don't know
mold me into her ? into him ? no
Mold me into her? Into him? No
little did you know , i ’m just me , let it go
Little did you know, I'm just me, let it go
lock me inside a pin of your perfection
correction
Lock me inside a pin of your perfection, correction
tear in ’ me down , am i what you like now ?
Tearin' me down, am I what you like now?
don ’t tell me what , what to do , what to say , what to think
about everything
Don't tell me what to do, what to say, what to think about everything
but did you ever think -
But did you ever think-
i ’ll say ~
I'll say~
good with bein ’ so bad
Good with bein' so bad
( so bad ~ )
(So bad~)
what ’s the issue ? i ’ll screw up again !
What's the issue? I'll screw up again!
yell out , scream and shout
Yell out, scream and shout
but i ’ll never change it now
But I'll never change it now
i ’m just too much but not enough to please you , right ?
I'm just too much but not enough to please you, right?
[ no i ’m never , never gonna - ]
[No I'm never, never gonna-]
your idea of ideals that you ’re screaming in my ear
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
i ’m just so broken ~
I'm just so broken~
never , never , never gonna figure it out !
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
comfortable and pathetic
i like it that way , get it ?
Comfortable and pathetic, I like it that way, get it?
you ’re brutal , judgemental , it ’s never that simple , but i still want -
You're brutal, judgemental, it's never that simple, but I still want-
to meet your harsh criteria
too bad i ’m never gonna
To meet your harsh criteria, too bad I'm never gonna
i ’m never gonna fit ~
[ fit ~ ! ]
I'm never gonna fit~ [Fit~!]
oh no ~
1, 2, 3 , go !
Oh no~ 1, 2, 3, go!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out!)
(Never gonna figure it out!)
Comfortable and pathetic,
I like it that way, get it?
You're brutal, judgmental,
it's never that simple, but I still want—
To meet your harsh criteria,
too bad I'm never gonna—
I'm never gonna fit~
Oh no~
To meet your harsh criteria,
too bad I'm never gonna...
I'm never gonna fit~
(Fit~!)
1, 2, 3, go!
(Ahh~!)
Yell out, scream and shout,
but I'll never change it now.
I'm just too much but not enough to please you, right?
(You, right~?)
[No, I'm never, never gonna—]
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear,
I'm just so broken~
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
I'll stop me!
I'll never figure it out~!
Hey! Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out!)